You drive me completely crazy.
Tu me rends completement fou.
Everything would be so simple if the kids weren't there.
Tout serait plus simple s'il n'y avait pas les enfants.
And if you didn't have such a nice ass.
Et si tu n'avais pas un si beau cul.
Where is that little
Oש est mon petit cul
peachy ass of mine?
super gיnial?
Little juicy, peachy ass.
petit cul, gיnial et juteux.
It's like a little alien coming from another planet.
C'est comme un petit alien venu d'une autre planטte.
Richard!
Richard!
What the fuck?
Qu'est ce qu'il y a ?
Oh, hum, Jennifer?
Oh, hum, Jennifer?
Just a friend.
Juste une amie.
She, uh... She came for two days before...
Elle, uh... Elle est arrivיe il y a 2 jours...
Anyway... Stan, Dimitri, my associates.
Bon quand mךme... Stan, Dimitri, mes associיs.
Hi.
Salut.
- Hi. - Hi...
- Salut. - Salut...
I'll leave you guys to it.
Je vous laisse les gars.
I'm gonna go take a shower.
Je vais aller prendre une douche.
Oh yeah, we got nothing to lose.
Oh ouais, on a rien א perdre.
As soon as I can, I'll fly far away.
Aussitפt que je peux, je vais partir loin.
Tell me where.
Dis moi oש.
I'll book my plane ticket right now.
Je vais rיserver mon billet d'avion tout de suite.
To L.A.
Vers L.A.
Everything is possible there.
Tout est possible lא bas.
Everything goes faster.
Tout va plus vite.
And... you can be noticed in no time.
Et... on peut te remarquer trטs vite.
And be noticed as what?
Et te remarquer comme quoi?
I don't know.
Je ne sais pas.
Just to be noticed?
Juste ךtre remarquיe?
You'd have to be blind not to notice you.
Il faudrait ךtre aveugle pour pas te remarquer.
- Fuck. Leave it. - What is it?
- Merde. Laisse חa. - Qu'est ce que c'est?
Peyote.
Du peyotl.
A local, highly powerful hallucinogenic. This shit
Un hallucinogטne local, trטs puissant. Cette merde
could flatten a football team.
pourrait יtendre raide toute une יquipe de foot.
It's for me!
C'est pour moi!
- For tonight! - Hey.
- Pour ce soir! - Hey.
This, plus weapons, is a guaranteed accident, you fucking morons.
חa, plus les armes, c'est l'accident garanti, foutus crיtins.
A few years ago, a Polish guy got so high on this shit,
Y'a quelques annיes, un polonais a יtי tellement barrי avec cette merde,
he sawed his own leg off without feeling a damn thing.
il s'est sciי la jambe entiטrement sans rien ressentir.
He died without a drop of blood in his body.
Il est mort sans verser une goutte de sang.
Here you go, beautiful. Could you go and hide it somewhere safe?
Te voilא, ma belle. Tu peux aller te cacher en sיcuritי?
Uh-oh, here comes trouble.
Uh-oh, voilא les ennuis.
Oh, yeah!
Oh, ouais!
No, no no no. No.
Non, non non non. Non.
Wow.
Wow.
Hey! There she is.
Hey! Elle est lא.
Oopsie, hang on a sec.
Oopsie, attend une sec.
There we go.
Nous voilא.
Oh. Richard went to give our passports to the gamekeeper.
Oh. Richard est allי donner nos passeports au garde chasse.
It'll take him all morning.
חa va lui prendre la matinיe.
Oh.
Oh.
And Dimitri is nursing a hangover.
Et Dimitri a la gueule de bois.
Which will also take all morning.
Ce qui va aussi durer la matinיe.
So.
Alors.
It's just the two of us.
Il y a juste nous deux.
- I'm gonna start packing. - Oh.
- Je vais faire les bagages. - Oh.
If I want to be ready on time.
Si je veux qu'on soit prךts א temps.
Oh, sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
Oh, dיsolי, je ne voulais pas t'effrayer.
Oh, no, it's OK, you just surprised me, that's all.
Oh, non, חa va, tu m'a juste surprise, c'est tout.
Hey, this is a nice bedroom.
Hey, c'est une belle chambre.
Yes, it is.
Oui, c'est vrai.
You know, it really is a shame
Tu sais, c'est vraiment dommage
we didn't have more time to get to know each other better.
qu'on ait pas eu plus de temps pour mieux se connaitre.
Call me when you can.
Appelle moi quand tu peux.
We could do...
Nous pourrions faire...
a thing or two...
une chose oub deux...
together.
ensemble.
I don't know if I'll have time with work.
Je ne sais pas si j'aurais du temps pour le travail.
Oh, work.
Oh, le travail.
So now you're a fucking politician.
Alors maintenant t'es un foutu politicien.
What is it you don't like about me?
Qu'est ce que tu n'aimes pas chez moi?
No, nothing.
Non, rien.
I just want to know, so...
Je veux juste savoir, alors...
tell me.
dis moi.
What is it you don't like about me?
Qu'est ce que tu n'aimes pas chez moi?
You're... You're not my type, that's all.
Tu... Tu n'est pas mon type, c'est tout.
Oh.
Oh.
Why am I not your type?
Pourquoi je suis pas ton type?
You're...
Tu...
you're too small.
tu es trop petit.
Oh.
Oh.
There we go!
Nous y voilא!
And I haven't changed height since yesterday, have I?
Et je n'ai pas changי de taille depuis hier, non?
I asked you a simple question.
Je t'ai posי une question simple.
Even for your tiny little oyster brain,
Mךme pour ta petite cervelle d'huitre,
it shouldn't be too difficult to understand.
חa doit pas ךtre trop difficile א comprendre.
So, I'll ask you again.
Alors, je te le redemande.
Did my height
Est ce que ma taille
change
a changי
since yesterday?
depuis hier?
No.
Non.
And yet, you seemed to like me yesterday.
Et pourtant, tu semblais bien m'aimer hier.
No, but I...
Non, mais je...
Yeah, yeah, yeah. When we were dancing together last night,
Ouais, Ouais, Ouais. Quand on dansaient ensemble hier,
everything was very clear.
tout יtait trטs clair.
You came onto me like a pussy in heat,
Tu es venue me voir comme une chatte en chaleur,
rubbing yourself against me,
te frottant contre moi,
turning me on.
me tournant autour.
And now, suddenly,
Et lא, soudainement,
I'm not your type?
je ne suis pas ton type?
Like that, boom.
Comme חa, boum.
During the night, I've become too small for you.
Pendant la nuit, je suis devenu trop petit pour toi.
Yesterday, you were dying for it.
Hier, tu le demandais.
And now you're apparently...
Et maintenant tu as appremment...
Stop--
Arrךte.
Richard will be back anytime soon.
Richard va revenir bientפt.
Oh, Richard.
Oh, Richard.
Hey.
Hey.
Call the helicopter.
Appelle l'hיlicoptטre.
I want to go home.
Je veux rentrer.
Hey, calm down, calm down.
Hey, calmes toi, calmes toi.
I'll take care of everything, OK?
Je m'occupe de tout, OK?
Don't worry.
T'inquiטtes pas.
How long did I sleep for?
J'ai dormi combien de temps?
Has the helicopter arrived yet? Shh...
- Lhיlicoptטre est dיjא arrivי? - Shh...
Everything's OK. I fixed everything.
Tout va bien. J'ai tout arrangי.
I made a few phone calls to find you a job.
J'ai passי quelques coups de fil pour te trouver un travail.
In Canada.
au Canada.
It's practically Los Angeles.
C'est presque Los Angeles.
That's the amount I transferred to an account for you,
C'est la somme que j'ai transfיrי sur un compte pour toi,
you can use it as you please.
tu peux l'utiliser comme tu veux.
Jen, this is the possibility to change your life,
Jen, c'est la possibilitי de changer ta vie,
to fulfill your dreams.
de rיaliser tes rךves.
I want to go home right now.
Je veux rentrer maintenant.
Call that fucking helicopter.
Appelle ce foutu hיlicoptטre.
Baby, baby, baby... Don't act like a child.
Bיbי, Bיbי, Bיbי... N'agis pas comme une enfant.
You know that's not possible.
Tu sais que c'est pas possible.
If you love me, think about me.
Si tu m'aimes, penses א moi.
OK, they fucked up big time,
OK, ils ont bien merdי,
but you're so damn beautiful, it's hard to resist you.
mais tu es si belle, c'est dur de te rיsister.
and we'll forget about the whole thing.
et on oubliera tout חa.
You call the goddamn helicopter!
Tu appelle ce bon sangn d'hיlicoptטre!
Or I'll call your wife and tell her everything!
Ou j'appelle ta femme et je lui dis tout!
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Mais merde tu te prends pour qui?
You little whore.
Petite pute.
Don't you ever talk about my wife.
Ne parles plus jamais de ma femme.
Don't you ever say her name.
Ne prononces plus jamais son nom.
Hey, stop! Stop! Stop!
Hey, stop! Stop! Stop!
Jen, look at me.
Jen, regarde moi.
I'm sorry about the slap.
Je suis dיsolי pour la giffle.
I didn't mean to hurt you. It's just... stress.
Je ne voulais pas te faire mal. C'est juste... le stress.
I lashed out without thinking.
C'est parti sans que j'y pense.
Give me your phone.
Donnes moi ton tיlיphone.
Give me the fucking phone!
Donnes moi le foutu tיlיphone!
I'm calling the chopper, I don't want to hear another word about it.
J'appelle l'hיlico, je veux plus rien entendre de tout חa.
What a fucking mess.
Quel foutu bordel.
Hey Roberto, it's Richard. How are you?
Hey Roberto, c'est Richard. Comment חa va?
I'm very good, thank you. Listen, we planned a pick-up at 2:30 pm.
Je vais bien, merci. Ecoute, on a prיvu une dיpose א 2:30 h.
Yeah. And I would like to make it earlier.
Ouais. Et j'aurais aimי que ce soit plus tפt.
Yeah, as soon as possible.
Ouais, aussi vite que possible.
Perfect.
Parfait.
OK, thanks.
OK, merci.
He'll be there in 30 minutes.
Je serai lא dans 30 minutes.
OK?
OK?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Take it easy! Take it easy!
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Du calme! Du calme!
Take it easy.
Du calme.
Did you really think I was that fucking stupid?
Tu penses vraiment que j'יtais si stupide?
A fucking idiot
Un foutu idiot
who will let his rifle loaded
qui allait laisser son flingue chargי
lying around for you to touch!
laissי lא pour que tu le touche!
Murder.
Meurtre.
Hey, beautiful.
Hey, beautי.
Peachy ass.
Joli petit cul.
What is it you don't like
Qu'est ce que tu n'aimes pas
about me?
chez moi?
Fuck! Fuck, fuck, fuck!
Merde! Merde, Merde, Merde!
Hi, guys! If you haven't heard of the hottest website
Salut, les gars! Si vous n'avez pas entendu parler du website le plus chaud
or shopping club in the US, tune in!
ou du club d'achat aux US, faites le!
We have some exciting news for you that's gonna help you save
Nous avons de super nouveautיs qui vont vous aider א יconomiser
thousands of dollars per year.
des milliers de dollars par an.
Log on to ShopClubUSA.com, or to make it easier
Connectez vous sur ShopClubUSA.com, ou plus facilement
you can also type in myscusa, M-Y-S-C-U-S-A,
vous pouvez taper myscusa, M-Y-S-C-U-S-A,
it stands for "shop club USA". Myscusa.com.
pour "shop club USA". Myscusa.com.
Both URLs will take you to the same mega-online shopping mall.
Ces URLs vous mיnerons aux mךme super online shopping mall.
We have thousands of products and if you sign up for a premier membership
Nous avons des milliers de produits et si vous vous inscsrivez comme membre premier
which is only 99 dollars a year, you're gonna get products
ce qui coute seulement 99 dollars par an, vous aurez des produits
at pretty much wholesale pricing for these items.
א presque le prix de gros.
Other retailers do not want you to know
Les autres vendeurs ne veulent pas que vous connaissiez
about ShopClubUSA.com.
ShopClubUSA.com.
We bring thousands of products, discounted from 30 to 80% off
Nous avons des milliers de produits, en promotion de 30 א 80%
like tablets, electronics, beauty, health and much much more.
comme des tablettes, des appareils, beautי, santי et bien plus.
You can sign up for a free membership and get up to 30% off items.
Vous pouvez vous inscrire librement et avoir un rabais de 30%.
Or if you can sign--
Ou vous pouvez signer...
Listen, let's...
Ecoute, on...
ShopclubUSA.com. Where deals are simply... irresistible.
- ShopclubUSA.com. Oש les achats sont simples.. - ...irrיsistibles.
Get your phones ready to dial...
Prיparez votre tיlיphone pour appeller...
...stands for ShopClubUSA. Myscusa.com.
...aller au ShopClubUSA. Myscusa.com.
And with a premier membership, get this, only 150$ for the I-Smart unit...
Et en יtant membre premier , vous avez, 150$ pour l'unitי I-Smart...
...plus the gloves, plus free shipping...
...plus les gants, plus l'envoi gratuit...
SCUSA has done it again!
SCUSA l'a encore fait!
Log on ShopClubUSA.com, search when you get there for the product...
Connectez vous sur ShopClubUSA.com, cherchez votre produit...
You can search for I-Smart...
Vous pouvez chercher l'I-Smart...
Hi, guys. If you haven't heard of the hottest website
Salut, les gars! Si vous n'avez pas entendu parler du website le plus chaud
or shopping club in the US...
ou du club d'achat aux US...
ShopClubUSA.com, where deals are simply... irresistible.
- ShopclubUSA.com. Oש les achats sont simples.. - ...irrיsistibles.
Ah, fuck!
Ah, merde!
Who the fuck do you think you are?
Pour qui te prends tu?
You think you're smart 'cause you could fuck those two assholes over?
Tu te crois maligne parce que tu as pu baiser ces deux trous du cul?
Those two fucking losers.
Ces deux foutus perdants.
And you thought you could win?
Et tu pensais que tu pouvais gagner?
Against me? The only moment that was possible
Contre moi? Le seul moment oש חa aurait יtי possible
was when I offered you to leave without putting up a fight.
c'יtait quand je t'ai offert de partir sans en faire une bataille.
But you had to put up a fight.
Mais tu as voulu une bataille.
Women always have to put up a fucking
Le sfemmes veulent tout le temps une foutue
fight.
bataille.
Retail value of this whole combo deal, over 400$.
Le prix de dיtail de ce combo , au dessus de 400$.
ShopClubUSA price, Scusa price, 175. Oh, my gosh.
le prix ShopClubUSA , Scusa, 175. Oh, mon vieux.
We are killing it today, giving you guys incredible deals--
Nous le faisons aujourdhui, en vous donnant d'incroyables prix...